download3000.com 2006-10-26

# Privacy policy - Download3000.com

This is the web site of "Download3000" ltd.

We can be reached via our [help desk](http://support.download3000.com/)

**Registration**  
In order to use some parts of this website (e.g. member areas), a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender or personal interests), and unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to use certain features of our bulletin board or other parts of the site that offer customized settings. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we "Download3000" ltd. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as email address.
